[{"Theme":"History","Questions":[{"Question":"The year of Lenin \u0027s birth?","Answers":[{"Answer":"1917","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"1870","IsCorrect":1},{"Answer":"1867","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"1900","IsCorrect":0}]},{"Question":"In what years was there a civil war in Russia?","Answers":[{"Answer":"1917-1922","IsCorrect":1},{"Answer":"1941-1945","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"1990-2022","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"1812-1814","IsCorrect":0}]},{"Question":"In what year was the Olympic Games held in Sochi?","Answers":[{"Answer":"2000","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"2011","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"1980","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"2014","IsCorrect":1}]},{"Question":"In what year was serfdom abolished in Russia?","Answers":[{"Answer":"1861","IsCorrect":1},{"Answer":"1995","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"2022","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"1812","IsCorrect":0}]},{"Question":"What was Stalin\u0027s name?","Answers":[{"Answer":"Moisha","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Joseph","IsCorrect":1},{"Answer":"Giuseppe","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Mikhail","IsCorrect":0}]}],"Level":"Normal","Top20":null},{"Theme":"Geography","Questions":[{"Question":"The capital of Russia is ...?","Answers":[{"Answer":"Ufa","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Saint-Petesburg","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Voronezh","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Moscow","IsCorrect":1}]},{"Question":"How many states are there in USA?","Answers":[{"Answer":"51","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"50","IsCorrect":1},{"Answer":"49","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"52","IsCorrect":0}]},{"Question":"How many poles does the Earth have","Answers":[{"Answer":"1","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"2","IsCorrect":1},{"Answer":"2,5","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"3","IsCorrect":0}]},{"Question":"The coldest ocean on Earth?","Answers":[{"Answer":"Southern","IsCorrect":1},{"Answer":"Arctic","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Indian","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Pacific","IsCorrect":0}]},{"Question":"Which country\u0027s capital is Ouagadougou?","Answers":[{"Answer":"Australia","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Burkina Faso","IsCorrect":1},{"Answer":"Russia","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Mozambique","IsCorrect":0}]}],"Level":"Easy","Top20":null},{"Theme":"Music","Questions":[{"Question":"The author of the opera Carmen?","Answers":[{"Answer":"Georges Bizet","IsCorrect":1},{"Answer":"Dieter Bohlen","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Michael Jackson","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Igor Stravinsky","IsCorrect":0}]},{"Question":"How many notes are there in a musical literacy?","Answers":[{"Answer":"12","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"32","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"7","IsCorrect":1},{"Answer":"64","IsCorrect":0}]},{"Question":"Which musical instrument doesn\u0027t have strings?","Answers":[{"Answer":"Guitar","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Piano","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Violin","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Drum","IsCorrect":1}]},{"Question":"Who didn\u0027t participate in the Beatles band?","Answers":[{"Answer":"Paul McCartney","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"John Lennon","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Harrison Ford","IsCorrect":1},{"Answer":"George Harrisson","IsCorrect":0}]},{"Question":"Which country is the ABBA from?","Answers":[{"Answer":"Russia","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Sweden","IsCorrect":1},{"Answer":"Poland","IsCorrect":0},{"Answer":"Switzerland","IsCorrect":0}]}],"Level":"Hard","Top20":null}]